<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ZEN">
    <Package name="Editor">
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_MoveDisplayToEdge">
            <English>Move Display to Edge</English>
            <Russian>Убрать панель за край</Russian>
            <German>Display an den Rand verschieben</German>
            <Polish>Przesuń wyświetlacz do krawędzi</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_MoveDisplayToEdge_Description">
            <English>Moves the Zeus Editor Display to the edge of the screen.</English>
            <German>Bewegt die Zeus Editor Anzeige an den Rand des Bildschirms.</German>
            <Polish>Przesuwa wyświetlacz edytora Zeusa do krawędzi ekranu.</Polish>
            <Russian>Убирает панель за край</Russian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_RemoveWatermark">
            <English>Remove Watermark</English>
            <Russian>Убрать водяной знак</Russian>
            <German>Wasserzeichen verstecken</German>
            <Polish>Usuń znak wodny</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_RemoveWatermark_Description">
            <English>Removes the watermark shown when hiding the display.</English>
            <German>Versteckt das Wasserzeichen, das gezeigt wird wenn die Oberfläche versteckt wird.</German>
            <Polish>Usuwa znak wodny pokazywany po ukryciu wyświetlacza.</Polish>
            <Russian>Убирает водяной знак ГМ когда интерфейс спрятан</Russian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DisableLiveSearch">
            <English>Disable Live Search</English>
            <Russian>Отключить мгновенный поиск</Russian>
            <German>Live Suche deaktivieren</German>
            <Polish>Wyłącz wyszukiwanie na żywo</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DisableLiveSearch_Description">
            <English>Requires pressing Enter or clicking the search button to confirm a search.\nHelps reduce lag when searching through a lot of items.</English>
            <German>Suche wird erst ausgeführt, wenn die Eingabetaste oder die Lupe neben dem Eingabefeld betätigt wird.\nHilft, Verzögerungen bei der Suche durch viele Elemente zu reduzieren.</German>
            <Polish>Wymaga wciśnięcia Enter lub kliknięcia przycisku wyszukiwania by potwierdzić wyszukiwanie.\nPomaga zredukować lag przy przeszukiwaniu wielu przedmiotów.</Polish>
            <Russian>Для подтверждения поиска тебуется нажатие клавиши Ввод\nПомогает уменьшить лаг при поиске </Russian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DeclutterEmptyTree">
            <English>Declutter Empty Tree</English>
            <Russian>Очистить пустое дерево</Russian>
            <German>Leer Kategorie aufräumen</German>
            <Polish>Oczyść drzewo pustych obiektów</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DeclutterEmptyTree_Description">
            <English>Declutters the empty tree by removing empty vehicles as those are available in the side specific trees.</English>
            <German>Räumt die Kategorie "Leer" auf. Leere Fahrzeuge werden versteckt, da diese in den Seiten spezifischen Kategorien vorhanden sind.</German>
            <Polish>Oczyszcza drzewo pustych obiektów przez usunięcie pustych pojazdów, gdyż są one dostępne w drzewach poszczególnych stron.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_UnitRadioMessages">
            <English>Unit Radio Messages</English>
            <Russian>Радиосообшения ИИ</Russian>
            <German>Funkmeldungen von Einheiten</German>
            <Polish>Wiadomość radiowa jednostki</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_UnitRadioMessages_Description">
            <English>Controls whether unit radio messages are played on placement and waypoint orders, waypoints only, or disabled.</English>
            <German>Steuert, ob die  Einheit eine Funkmeldung absetzt wenn diese platziert wird und eine Anweisung von Wegpunkten erhält oder nur bei Wegpunkten oder niemals.</German>
            <Polish>Kontroluje czy wiadomości radiowe jednostki są odtwarzane przy postawieniu i wyznaczeniu punktu trasy, jedynie przy wyznaczeniu punktu trasy lub czy są wyłączone.</Polish>
            <Russian>Определяет будут ли ИИ подразделения сообщать по радио о своих действиях или нет.</Russian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_UnitRadioMessages_WaypointsOnly">
            <English>Waypoints Only</English>
            <Russian>Только путевые точки</Russian>
            <German>Nur Wegpunkte</German>
            <Polish>Tylko punkty trasy</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_ToggleIncludeCrew">
            <English>Toggle Include Crew</English>
            <German>Besatzung hinzufügen umschalten</German>
            <Polish>Przełącz 'dołącz załogę'</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_EjectPassengers">
            <English>Eject Passengers</English>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_EjectPassengers_Description">
            <English>Ejects the passengers of all selected vehicles. If the vehicle is currently flying, the units will be given parachutes.\nUnlike vanilla eject, units will disembark one after another (not immediately, with a short delay in-between).</English>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DeployCountermeasures">
            <English>Deploy Countermeasures</English>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Editor_DeployCountermeasures_Description">
            <English>Makes all selected vehicles deploy countermeasures such as smokes and flares.</English>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
