<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ZEN">
    <Package name="Camera">
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_DisplayName">
            <English>Camera</English>
            <Russian>Камера</Russian>
            <French>Caméra</French>
            <German>Kamera</German>
            <Czech>Kamera</Czech>
            <Italian>Camera</Italian>
            <Polish>Kamera</Polish>
            <Japanese>カメラ</Japanese>
            <Korean>카메라</Korean>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_FollowTerrain">
            <English>Follow Terrain</English>
            <Russian>Следование Рельефу</Russian>
            <French>Suivre le terrain</French>
            <German>Geländeform folgen</German>
            <Czech>Sleduj terén</Czech>
            <Italian>Segui il terreno</Italian>
            <Polish>Śledz Teren</Polish>
            <Japanese>地形追随</Japanese>
            <Korean>지형 따라가기</Korean>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_FollowTerrain_Description">
            <English>Controls whether the camera's height should adjust with changes in terrain elevation.</English>
            <Russian>Контролирует должна ли высота камеры регулироваться при изменении высоты местности</Russian>
            <French>Contrôle si la hauteur de la caméra doit être ajustée en fonction des changements d'élévation du terrain.</French>
            <German>Steuert, ob sich die Höhe der Kamera bei Änderungen der Geländehöhe anpassen soll.</German>
            <Czech>Určuje, zda by se měla výška kamery upravovat podle změn výšky terénu.</Czech>
            <Japanese>標高に合わせてカメラの高さを変化させます。</Japanese>
            <Korean>지형의 고도 변화에 따른 카메라 높이 조정 여부를 제어합니다.</Korean>
            <Polish>Kontroluje czy kamera podąża względem wysokości terenu.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_AdaptiveSpeed">
            <English>Adaptive Speed</English>
            <Russian>Адаптивная Скорость</Russian>
            <French>Vitesse adaptive</French>
            <German>Adaptive Geschwindigkeit</German>
            <Czech>Adaptivní rychlost</Czech>
            <Polish>Prędkość adaptacyjna</Polish>
            <Italian>Velocità adattiva</Italian>
            <Japanese>順応型速度</Japanese>
            <Korean>속도 자동 조절</Korean>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_AdaptiveSpeed_Description">
            <English>Adapts the camera's speed based on its current height. Lower height - slower camera movement.</English>
            <Russian>Адаптирует скорость камеры в зависимости от ее текущей высоты. Чем ниже высота - тем медленее движение камеры.</Russian>
            <French>Adapte la vitesse de la caméra en fonction de sa hauteur actuelle. Hauteur plus basse - mouvement plus lent de la caméra.</French>
            <German>Passt die Geschwindigkeit der Kamera an die aktuelle Höhe an. Geringere Höhe bedeutet langsamere Kamerabewegungen.</German>
            <Czech>Upravuje rychlost kamery na základě jeho aktuální výšky. Nižší výška - pomalejší pohyb kamery.</Czech>
            <Japanese>現在のカメラの高さに応じてカメラ速度が順応します。低高度では速度が遅くなります。</Japanese>
            <Korean>현재 높이에 따라 카메라의 속도를 조정합니다. 낮은 고도에서는 카메라가 느리게 움직입니다.</Korean>
            <Polish>Steruje prędkością kamery względem obecnej wysokości, czym wyżej tym szybciej, czym niżej tym wolniej.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_DefaultSpeedCoef">
            <English>Default Speed Coefficient</English>
            <Russian>Коэффициент Скорости По Умолчанию</Russian>
            <French>Coefficient de vitesse par défaut</French>
            <German>Standardmäßiger Geschwindigkeitskoeffizient</German>
            <Czech>Výchozí koeficient rychlosti</Czech>
            <Polish>Współczynnik prędkości domyślnej </Polish>
            <Italian>Coefficente velocità default</Italian>
            <Japanese>カメラ標準係数</Japanese>
            <Korean>기본 속도 계수</Korean>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_DefaultSpeedCoef_Description">
            <English>Coefficient for the default camera movement speed, higher is faster.</English>
            <Russian>Коэффициент для скорости движения камеры по умолчанию. Чем выше тем быстрее.</Russian>
            <French>Coefficient pour la vitesse de mouvement par défaut de la caméra, plus elle est élevée, plus elle est rapide.</French>
            <German>Koeffizient für die Standard-Bewegungsgeschwindigkeit der Kamera, höher ist schneller.</German>
            <Czech>Koeficient pro výchozí rychlost pohybu kamery, vyšší je rychlejší.</Czech>
            <Japanese>カメラの標準移動速度を決定する係数で、高いほど早くなります。</Japanese>
            <Korean>기본 카메라 움직임 속도의 계수입니다. 계수가 높을수록 속도가 빠릅니다.</Korean>
            <Polish>Współczynnik domyślnej prędkości kamery, wyższa wartość równa się szybciej.</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_FastSpeedCoef">
            <English>Fast Speed Coefficient</English>
            <Russian>Коэффициент Быстрой Скорости</Russian>
            <French>Coefficient de vitesse rapide</French>
            <German>Koeffizient für schnelle Geschwindigkeit</German>
            <Czech>Vysokorychlostní koeficient</Czech>
            <Polish>Współczynnik szybkiej prędkości</Polish>
            <Japanese>速度係数</Japanese>
            <Korean>빠른 속도 계수</Korean>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ZEN_Camera_FastSpeedCoef_Description">
            <English>Coefficient for the fast camera movement speed (when holding down the shift key), higher is faster.</English>
            <Russian>Коэффициент для быстрой скорости движения камеры (когда зажата клавиша shift). Чем выше тем быстрее.</Russian>
            <French>Coefficient pour la vitesse de mouvement rapide de la caméra (en maintenant la touche shift enfoncée), plus haut est plus rapide.</French>
            <German>Koeffizient für die schnellere Kamerabewegungsgeschwindigkeit (bei gedrückter Shift-Taste), höher ist schneller.</German>
            <Czech>Koeficient pro vysokou rychlost pohybu kamery (při přidržení klávesy Shift), vyšší je rychlejší.</Czech>
            <Japanese>カメラの移動速度を決定する係数 (Shift 長押し時) で、高いほど早くなります。</Japanese>
            <Korean>빠른 카메라의 이동을 위한 계수 (Shift 키를 누르고 있을때), 계수가 높을수록 속도가 빠릅니다.</Korean>
            <Polish>Wspólczynnik szybkiego ruchu kamery (naciskając shift), wyższa wartość równa się szybciej</Polish>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
